<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>High Tech Laboratory Facilities (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.HighTechLaboratoryFacilities</packageId>
  <author>Pravus</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/HighTechLaboratoryFacilities</url>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of Pravus mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=841760538

- Added an option to hide the apparel added by the mod
- Fixed the coloring of the benches added by the mod
- For those who want the old color of the benches they will now have the old color when made of Plasteel

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/HighTechLaboratoryFacilities][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]

New and redesigned laboratory facilities for a more high tech look!


This mod started out as a personal project for myself to use in my own game but due to requests I decided to release it publicly. I made this mod due to feeling that the graphics for the "hi-tech research bench" and "comms console" were a bit too boring and plain for my liking so I decided to make my own graphics for them. Following that I decided to continue modifying and adding research assets to fit the theme I was working toward. Full disclosure, I didn't work on this mod to the point that I would normally consider fully finished and there are a few parts I never felt fully satisfied with (the ground-penetrating scanner graphic being one example as I never could come up with a fully realized design that I liked). I am also currently playing other games and focusing on other matters in my life so I doubt I'll undertake any further updates anytime soon. To make up for that however I included a little bonus:

- tailor-made lab coats that slightly enhance research skills
- a late game research project that unlocks plans for an advanced powered combat exoskeleton
- custom graphics for both (exoskeleton artwork based upon the incomparable rooki1's work!)

Quick and dirty update! Added native minification def to all items due to popular request. All usable research items (Hi-Tech Research Bench, Laboratory Station, and Research Terminal) now link with the MultiAnalyzer and each other for a benefit of +10% research speed per link. This hopefully makes up for the Laboratory Station and Research Terminal not counting as Hi-Tech Research Benches for the purpose of actively researching technologies with the bench specifically noted as a prerequisite. Enjoy!

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>

